http://www.mpexperts.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

Privacy Notice
This Security and Privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for http://www.MPExperts.com. This statement does not apply to the practices of companies that MPExperts.com does not own or to people that MPExperts.com does not employ.
Commitment To Privacy:
MPExperts.com values its customers and respects their privacy. In connection with demonstrating its commitment to your privacy, MPExperts.com has agreed to disclose its information and privacy and security practices. If you feel that MPExperts.com is not abiding by its posted privacy and security practices, you should contact our customer service department at 1-731-426-2044.
Information We Collect and Use:
We collect information about you (such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, e-mail/IP address, transactions with us, and credit card number) that you provide when you place an order or that you provide to us in any other way. We may acquire customer names, e-mail addresses or mailing addresses for select mailings from third parties. We use the information that you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, communicating with you, improving our services, conducting research, providing anonymous reporting for existing and prospective clients or advertisers, and processing and confirming your order. From time to time, we may also use your information to notify you about our products, services, contests, or promotions. Except as otherwise provided herein, we do not sell or rent the information that you provide to us online to third parties.
Ordering:
We request information from you on our order form. Here, a customer must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (credit card number, expiration date, and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes to verify the customer is of legal age, and to fill customers' orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies:
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the end-user's hard drive containing information that relates directly to the end-user's visit to our web site. MPExperts.com may, from time to time, use cookies. Any information placed in the cookie is accessible only to MPExperts.com, and will not be sold or shared with anyone else. In the event that we use cookies, we do so to improve your shopping experience as cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our customers to enhance the experience on our site. You may change your browser to prevent your browser from accepting cookies.
Sharing of Information:
We value your privacy at MPExperts.com, and will not release any personally identifiable account information to anyone outside of the necessary core groups that help our business function unless our customers give us the authority to do so or otherwise in accordance with this privacy and security statement. We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information, however, is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may from time to time use an outside shipping company to ship orders or a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. Additionally, we may contract with third parties to assist us in maintaining or managing our customer information. In such events, we will advise these companies not to retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We may be required to use your information to respond to court orders or subpoenas or to establish or exercise our legal rights or to defend against legal claims. We may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law. We may transfer your information if MPExperts.com or the assets thereof are acquired by or merged with another company.
Links:
In the event that this web site contains links to other sites, please be aware that MPExperts.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Security:
When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the encryption software - SSL (Secure Socket Layers), provided by Godaddy.com, a premier encryption software company. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take actions to protect user-information offline. Our users' information is generally restricted in our offices. Our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance of keeping our customers' information secure and safe at all times. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a locked and secure environment.
Children:
Please note that if you are under 18, you may purchase products from MPExperts.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
Correcting/Updating Personal Information:
If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your shipping or billing address, your preferred credit card, etc.), you can add new information or delete any addresses or credit cards from your account on our website or you may obtain live one-on-one help by phone at 1-731-426-2044.
Notification of Changes:
If we decide to change our privacy and security statement, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy and security statement under which the information was collected.
Agreement to Privacy and Security Statement:
By using our Web site, you agree to the MPExperts.com privacy and security statement as provided above.
Back
Site Map
Copyright © 2020 Global Military Police Experts, LLC. Site by Anvil IT Solutions, Inc.
